Guide to the Michael Anania Papers circa 1950s-2006
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Manuscripts by Anania
  - "The Detective Story, or rather an Account of Part of a Day Considering Writing a Detective Story," undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "The Diagram," undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "Dialogue," undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Die Fremde," undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - "Dig, and Dig Deep," undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "Divertissment," undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - "Documents: Proem," undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - "Dorothy and the Wizard," undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "Doubling Back," undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - "Down in the Cellar and Back Again," undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - "Draw-Knife," undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "The Dream of Self-Reliance and the Cybernetic Meadow," undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Driving Back," 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Earth Day, 1990," 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Ed Colker’s Assemblage of Years," undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "An Elegy for Edward Hopper," 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "The End of the String," undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "An Epistle to Francis Pettis, Esq.," undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "An Errand," undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Evanston Talk, "Preparing Students for College," undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Evvoia," 2004. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "The Eye’s Geography: Locutions of Place in the Poetry of John Mattias," 1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "Factum, Chansons, Etc," undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "Feminist Criticism," undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "Figures in a Landscape," undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "The Finality of a Poem," undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - "Five in Passing," undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Five Proper Nouns from Johannes Bobrowski," undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "The Flower and the Leaf," undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "The Flower of Agathon," undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Focus on Writing," undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - "For a Centenial Pagent," undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - "For a Friend Near Forty," undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "Forgetting the Eighties," undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "Four Brief Fictionales on a Motif by Phyllis Moore," undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - "Four Exemplary Texts," undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "Four O’Clocks," undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - "Four Very Short Plays," undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "Fragments of a Remembered Omaha," undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - "From Realism to Romance," undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - "From the Top," undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - "The Future of the Institutions of the Printed Word," 1993 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Gardening the Skies, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - "A Garland for Eugene Wildman," undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Gass Introduction, The Arts Club, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - "George Washington," undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "The Girl of the Golden West," undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - "Golden Spike," undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - "Grant Park, Thursday Evening," undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - "The Great Well," undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - "Hands," undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - "Harriet Monroe in Russia Reading Pound," undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Heat Lines, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Heat Lines, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Heat Lines, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Heat Lines, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Heat Lines, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Her Morning Toilet," undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Her Voyage," undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Here and There," undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "Herman, the Grizzly Bear," undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "Hidden Treasures," undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Historical Marker," undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Home Again," undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "I Do Not Know This Sadness…," 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "In a Field in Illinois," undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "In a Man’s Imagination or Before Him on His Page," undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "In Any Event," undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - In Natural Light, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - In Natural Light, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - In Natural Light, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - In Natural Light, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - In Natural Light, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - In Natural Light, "What Are Islands to Me Now," 2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - In Plain Sight, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - In Plain Sight, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - In Plain Sight, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - In Plain Sight, "An Insider’s Guide to Teenspeak," 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - In Plain Sight, "O Lana Turner we love you get up": Popular Elements in Contemporary Poetry," 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - In Plain Sight, "Of Living Belfry and Rampart: On American Literary Magazines Since 1950," undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - In Plain Sight, "Starting," 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - In Plain Sight, "The Ties that Bind," undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "In the Blue Distance," undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "In the Day-Room," undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "In the Wilderness," undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "Inliers, Outliers: On Paul Metcalf’s Apalache," undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "’It Quickens,’ Figures of Conception, Birth and Renewal and the Poetics of Change," undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "January Suite," undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - "Jesse," undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - "Jurassic Landscape," undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Karl Shapiro, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - "Karl Shapiro: An Interview on Poetry," undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - "Kilowatt Hour," undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "King Drive," undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Knots," undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "The Lady in the Seed," undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Langue de Boeuf: A Garland for the Whole Gang," undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "Leaving the Wake," undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "The Legend of Good Women," 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "Letter I," undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Lines Composed Above Portland," 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Lines for a Friend," undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Little Miss Sad," undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Loons," undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - "Lottos Turannos," undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "Lucien in Homer Row," undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - "Lunchcounter Fragments," undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "Lyon Street Variations," undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Making It News: The Mandate for Originality [Change] in Literary Magazines," 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "Malvern," undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "The Man on the Turquoise House," undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "La Manvaise Terre," undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - "Many Happy Returns," undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - "Matters of Chance and Beauty," undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "Max Michelson Preface," undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - "A Measured Response," undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "Meat and Potatoes" Proposal, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - "Melancholia," undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Melus Conference, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - "The Memorial," undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - "Mirrors," undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - "Modern Poetics," undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - "Moments for a January Afternoon," undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - "A Moment’s Praise," undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - "Montage Noël," undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - "My Mother’s Poem," undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - "The Mysteries of Women," undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - "Names," undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - National Conference of State Legislature, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - "Nativity," 1962 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - "Nelson Algren and the City," undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - New Poetry Anthology, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - "Night Passage to En-Dor," undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - "No Curv Service," undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - "Nobody’s Heart," undated (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - "Not That Fair Field," undated (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - "Note to an Elegist," undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - "Notes to the War Zone," undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - "November or Else: An Ode," undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - "Nuit de Saint Sylvestre (Paris 1957)," undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - "Oda a Unas Flores Amarillas," undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - "Ode to the Cowboy, Drilled Ag’in," undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - "Off Race Point," 1960 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - "On Landscape Towards a Proper Silence," undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - "On Literary Criticism," undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - "On the Death of Waters," undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - "On the Trail of the Pirroetting Plaid Elephant," undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Once Again, Flowered, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - "The Only Game in Town," undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - "Open as Plain Air," undated (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - "An Orcas Addendum," undated (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - "Otero," undated (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - "Out West," undated (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Outline, Cities, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - "Palimpsest," undated (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Paper, Rocks, Scissors, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Pat Nelson Memorial, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Pavanne," undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "The Payment," undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Person – a Condition of Place," undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Phantasmagoria," undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "A Place that’s Known," undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - "Places," undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - "Pochade," undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Poem," undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Poems and Drafts for the ‘60s, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - "Poems Beginning With Words from Barbara Guest," undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "Poetics," undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "The Poetics of Politics and the Politics of Poetics," undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - "Poetry and Process," undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - "Poetry in an Age of Urgent Belief," undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - "Potatoes," undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - "A Precision of Interest," undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - "Prokofiev," undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - "Puppet Show in Frankfurt," undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - "Ralph – A Play in One Act," undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - "Reading Yeats in a Chicago Church," 2003 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - "Recurring Questions," undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - "A Red Cloud," undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - The Red Menace, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - The Red Menace, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - The Red Menace, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - The Red Menace, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Remembering Winter," undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - "Remembering You," undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Response" to Kenneth Koch, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Riversongs, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Riversongs, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Riversongs, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Riversongs, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Riversongs, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Riversongs, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Rivets, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "The Role of the University-Based Literary Magazine," 1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Rosa Addurusa," undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "Round Song," undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Satisfaction Guaranteed or Proposition for a Late Spring Day," undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Scat," undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Scissors, Stones and Paper: A Historic View of Censorship and Literature," 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Screen Gems," undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Sculling," undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "Sears Tower," undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Selected Poems, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Selected Poems, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Selected Poems, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Selected Poems, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Set/Sorts, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "Setting Out," undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "Seven Pieces for Unaccompanied Voice," undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Shadow Puppets," undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Shelvings," undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "The Silences," undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The Sky at Ashland, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - The Sky at Ashland, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Sky at Ashland, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The Sky at Ashland, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - The Sky at Ashland, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Sky at Ashland, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Snapshot," 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "Snow, Ice and Cold," undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "Some Couplets," undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "Some Curiosities in Place of a Definition," undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - "Some Lines for Big Walter Horton," undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - "Some Summers," undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - "Some Things," undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - "Some Words for Laura Dean," undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - "Song," undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - "Song for the Fourteenth Marriage of Mrs. P." undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - "Sonnett on a broken type r ter," undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - "Sortes Chicagoanum," undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - "Squares," undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - "Stanzas: As Light Breaks," undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - "Statement for ARIEL (Triton College)," undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - "The Story of Witch, Also Called Goat," undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - "A Strategem," undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - "Stroll," undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - "Substance and Prosody," undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - "Suburban Autumn," undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - "The Sunset Through Curtains in April," undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - "The Sweet Remembered Demarcations," undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - "Sweetsong," undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - "Tarsus," undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - "Text for ILLINOIS EXHIBIT," undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - "The Thirteenth Labor, or the Writer in the World," undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - "This is Just to Say," undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - "Three Episodes in Lieu of a Novel," undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - "Three Improvisations on a Line from Kenneth Koch," undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - "Three to Get Ready," undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - "Tiergarten," undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - "Tierra del Fuego," undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - "’To Play the Loser’s End of a Fine Venture’: On Literary Magazines," undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - "To Yourself," undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - "Toward Ceylon," undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - "Triste Traffique," undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - "Twenty Year Document," undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - "Two Fisherman," undated (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - "The Unmoving Cloud," undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - "Upstanding," 1978 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - "V.S. Naipaul Introduction," 1991 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - "Valences," undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - "Valentine’s Day," undated (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - "Valentines," 1969 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - "Variations on Arrival," undated (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - "The Versatile Dream," undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - "Violets," undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - "Virginia Woolf and Tight Jeans," undated (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - "Waiting There," undated (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - "Walk in Beauty," undated (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - "Walpurgisnacht," undated (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - "’The Warm Tympanic Page’: Donald Barthelme and the Written Voice," undated (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - "Watering Plants," undated (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - "The Way Back," undated (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - "The Well," undated (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - "Western Improvisations," undated (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - "What Goes Up – Novel," undated (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - "What it Means to Be a Poet in America: ‘The Private Act and the Public Voice’," undated (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - "Which Less is More? Literature, Audience and the Search for Cultural Consequences," undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Wierd Harold," undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "With Cyrus Coulter Toward 47th Street," undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Word-Play," 1973 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Words," undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Write On," undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "You Can’t Tell the Program Without the Players," undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "You, There," undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Untitled Poems, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Untitled Poems, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Untitled Poems, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Untitled Poems, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Untitled Poems, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Untitled Writings, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Untitled Writings, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Untitled Writings, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Untitled Writings, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Series V: Manuscripts by Others
  - Addozino, Kim, "Reading," undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Agostino, Enzo, 1997, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Alexander, Floyd, "Episodes on the Floor of the Sky; Poems," undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Jeffrey Renard, "Stellar Places; Poems," undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Jeffrey Renard, "Stellar Places; Poems," undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Jeffrey Renard, "Stellar Places; Poems," undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Allen, Jeffrey Renard, 1990-1998 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Alter, Robert, "Mimesis and the Motive for Fiction," undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Amann, Jürg, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Elliott and Adrianne Fincham, "Minus One," 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Elliott, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Antin, David, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Archambeau, Robert, "A Cage Holding More Than a Mouse: James McMichael," undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Archambeau, Robert, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ashley, Robert, "Atalanta (Acts of God)," 1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Atlas, James, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Austin, John, "Journeys," undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bawer, Bruce, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Bellamy, Joe David, "American Poetry Observed," undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Bellamy, Joe David, "American Poetry Observed," undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Bellamy, Joe David, "American Poetry Observed," undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Biddings, Mary, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Boer, Charles, "Charles Olson in Mans-Field," undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Boer, Charles, "The Man Who Shot Henry James," 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Boer, Charles, "The Morgan Touch: The Complete Poems of J. Pierpont Morgan and Company," undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Boer, Charles, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Boez, Marc, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Bray, Robert, "The Regionalist Tradition in Midwestern Poetry: Minor Leagues or Minor Key?," 1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Breedlove, John, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Brent, Frances, Reunions and Other Poems, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Buchanan, Mrs. Douglas, Robert Desnos: Translations, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Burns, Gerald, Letters to Obscure Men, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Burns, Gerald, The Myth of Accidence, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Burns, Gerald, Sonnets From the Middle English, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Burns, Gerald, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Callner, David, "A Collection of Tanka by Kisaburo Konoshima," undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Caramella, Alberto, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - a Carino, Maria Luisa, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Chambers, George, Poems, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Chernoff, Maxine, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Claire, William F., 1968 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Cole, Peter, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Cook, Albert, Forces: Modern and Postmodern Poetic Structures, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Cook, Albert, Forces: Modern and Postmodern Poetic Structures, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cook, Albert, Modes, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Cook, Albert, "New Musics in Poetry: The Senses of Sound," undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Albert, 1982-1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Corrington, Harold, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Creeley, Robert, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Cumberland, David, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Cycholl, Garin Lee, Thesis "Blue Mound to 161 and Shorter Poems," 1999 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Cycholl, Garin Lee, "Topics in Experimental Photography," undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Davidson, Cynthia, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Deanovich, Connie, Xylophone Luncheonette, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Detro, Gene, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - di Camillo, Kevin T.P., 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Doria, Charles, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Edlow, Cynthia Schwartzberg, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ehrhart, W.D., undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - England, Amy, Flute Ship, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Farrell, Kate, Goodbye Kathy Dougherty and Other Poems, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Federman, Raymond, Surfiction: Now and Tomorrow, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Federman, Raymond, Take It or Leave It, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Federman, Raymond, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Finchman, Adrianne, "Winter Kill," undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Fox, Siv Cedering, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Fredman, Steve, "Call Him Charles," 1993 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Gale, Vi, Clearwater, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Gallagher, Cynthia, Earth Elegance, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Ganzer, Carol, White Gloves, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Gibbons, Reginald, Sparrow: Poems, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Gibbons, Reginald, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Goldberg, Bertrand, Architectural Fables, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Graham, Lea, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Grathwohl, Susan, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Guest, Barbara, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Hall, Donald, "Poetry: The Unsayable Said," 1993 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Hammond, Mac, Mappamundi, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, Mac, 1972-1996 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Harper, Susan, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Harr, Barbara, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Hietter, James, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Higgins, Dick, "Seen, Heard and Understood," undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Higginson, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Hollow, Anselm, Selected Poems 1959-1969, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Honig, Edwin, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Hughes, Mary Gray, "The Stuttering Priest," undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Huk, Romana, "Interview: Denise Riley," 1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Hunt, William, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Hurkey, Rooan, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Inglehart, Babette F., "Margaret Anderson: A Biographical/Critical Study," undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Jacob, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Kaplan, Carla, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Kasper, Catherine, Dissertation "A New Wave of Miracles Stuns the World," 1999 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Kasper, Catherine, Encyclopedia of Stones, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Kasper, Catherine, Field Stone, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Kasper, Catherine, Thesis Lives of the Saints, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Kasper, Catherine, The Transparent Eyeball, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Kasper, Catherine, 2001-2003 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Kerrigan, Anthony, "The Night one Nobel Threw Another Nobel Out of His House: A Participant’s Memoir," undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Kitchkommie, Cecil, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Klein, Ruth, "10 Poems," 1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Kleinzahler, August, Earthquake Weather, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)